slim9.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

This is the web site of Slim9 Weight Loss Pills 

Our postal address is: 

PO BOX 65511  
1365 Beaumont Ave.  
Montreal, Quebec  
H3P 3H8  
Canada 

We can be reached via e-mail at our contact us page or you can reach us by telephone at 1-877-79-SLIM9 (75469) 

As each patients privacy is greatly important to us, Slim9 will never disclose any personal information to any third-parties. Your name, e-mail address and all other personal information will not be sold or used for any other purpose than processing your order. Information such as your telephone number and e-mail address are optional and only assist us in providing order confirmations and tracking information. 

A bank processor under strict guidelines keeps required information such as credit card numbers, names and address, in order to prevent fraud. Orders, which do not meet certain criteria, may be subject to cancellation at the discretion of Slim9. Financial information will not be viewed or accessible to any internal personnel and is only stored for the time necessary for order processing. 

Using a 256-Bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, any orders processed online are safe and secure. No personal or financial information is stored on internal servers and are processed through our secure server, in order to protect each of our clients’ security and privacy. 

Slim9 will never solicit via telephone, fax, e-mail or direct mail, this is strictly against our policy and we adhere strictly to them. Each client’s safety, security and privacy is of great importance to us, and our policies are designed to protect each patient. If you have any questions or concerns pertaining to our Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us using our Contact form. 

  1. For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.
  2. We collect user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., billing address).
  3. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded.
  4. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart.
  5. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.
  6. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.
  7. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.
  8. With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
  9. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
  10. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.
